David Stick Papers PC.5001
State Archives of North Carolina
- Writings, 1813-2009 and undated (bulk 1939-2009); 1939-2009; 45073; 1.000; Stick, David, 1919-2009
  - The Outer Banks of North Carolina, 1939-1991; 6963; 1.000; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    - Writing, 1955-1991; 6971; 1.000; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Drafts, 1956-1958; 6972; Stick, David, 1919-2009
        - Parts 1 and 2: Fourth Draft [2 folders], circa 1956; 28085; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Parts 1 and 2: Fourth Draft [2 folders])
        - Part 3: First Draft, circa 1958; 28086; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Part 3: First Draft)
        - Part 4: First Draft, January 1958; 28087; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Part 4: First Draft)
        - Part 1: Rewrites, 1958; 28088; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Part 1: Rewrites)
        - Part 2: Rewrites, 1958; 28089; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Part 2: Rewrites)
        - Part 3: Rewrites, 1958; 28090; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Part 3: Rewrites)
        - Annotated Proofs, 1958; 29324; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Annotated Proofs)
        - Guide to Points of Interest, circa 1958; 28091; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Guide to Points of Interest)
        - Part 1, 1958; 28092; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Part 1)
        - Part 2, 1958; 28093; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Part 2)
        - Part 3, 1958; 28094; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Part 3)
        - Part 4, 1958; 28095; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Part 4)
        - Index, 1958; 28096; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Index)
        - Efforts to Create a Major Port, circa 1958; 28097; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Efforts to Create a Major Port)
        - New Life for the Banks, 1958; 28098; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder New Life for the Banks)
        - Other Chapters: Outlines, Additions, Fragments, circa 1958; 28099; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Other Chapters: Outlines, Additions, Fragments)
        - Undated Draft [2 folders], circa 1958; 28100; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Undated Draft [2 folders])
      - Reviews and Clippings, 1958-1991; 28101; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Reviews and Clippings)
      - Illustrations, 1958; 28102; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Illustrations)
      - Index Cards, circa 1958; 28103; 1.000; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Box Index Cards)
  - An Outer Banks Reader, 1991-2006; 6721; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    This subseries contains drafts, publication information, and research files on one of Stick's later publications, An Outer Banks Reader. This work consists of narratives on various topics in Outer Banks history collected, edited, and annotated by David Stick. Research material in this subseries primarily consists of photocopies of documents utilized by David Stick in his research, organized by document title or grouped together by subject. No original material is in these folders.
    - Drafts and Publication Information, 1991-1999; 6992; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Contract, 1996-1998; 28104; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Contract)
      - UNC Press Miscellaneous, 1998; 28105; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder UNC Press Miscellaneous)
      - Correspondence, 1996; 28106; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence)
      - Correspondence, 1995; 28107; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence)
      - Correspondence, 1994; 28108; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence)
      - Correspondence, 1991-1992; 28109; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence)
      - Chronology, 1995; 28110; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Chronology)
      - Reprint Permission, 1997; 28111; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Reprint Permission)
      - Current, 1997; 28112; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Current)
      - Lists of Contents, 1993-1995; 28113; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Lists of Contents)
      - Headnotes (Original Stick Headnotes Before Revision), circa 1994; 28114; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Headnotes (Original Stick Headnotes Before Revision))
      - Categories, 1990s; 28115; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Categories)
      - Miscellaneous, 1991-1995; 28116; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
      - Notes, 1992-1993; 28117; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notes)
      - Reviews, 1998-1999; 28118; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Reviews)
      - Reader Responses, 1998-1999; 28119; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Reader Responses)
      - Publicity, 1998; 28120; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Publicity)
      - Wynne Dough, 1996-1998; 28121; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Wynne Dough)
      - Royalties, 1998; 28122; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Royalties)
      - UNC Press - Index, etc., 1997-1998; 28123; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder UNC Press - Index, etc.)
      - UNC Press Publicity Story and Pictures, 1998; 28124; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder UNC Press Publicity Story and Pictures)
      - Proof Copy, circa 1998; 28125; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Proof Copy)
    - Research Material, 1990s-2006; 6993; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - The Evolution of An Outer Banks Reader, David Stick, 2006; 28126; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder The Evolution of An Outer Banks Reader, David Stick)
      - Notes on Chapter Arrangement, 1990s; 28127; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notes on Chapter Arrangement)
      - Notes on Items Considered but Not Included by the Publisher, 1990s; 28128; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notes on Items Considered but Not Included by the Publisher)
      - Notes on Topics Considered for An Outer Banks Reader, 1990s; 28129; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notes on Topics Considered for An Outer Banks Reader)
      - Detail of Manuscript Map of the World, Gerolamo de Verrazano, 1529, 1990s; 28130; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Detail of Manuscript Map of the World, Gerolamo de Verrazano, 1529)
      - The Towne of Secota, Theodor de Bry, 1590, 1990s; 28131; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder The Towne of Secota, Theodor de Bry, 1590)
      - Colonial Records of North Carolina Excerpts, 1654-1678, 1990s; 28132; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Colonial Records of North Carolina Excerpts, 1654-1678)
      - Relief for the Indians of the Outer Banks, 1714, Colonial Records of North Carolina vol. II, 1990s; 28133; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Relief for the Indians of the Outer Banks, 1714, Colonial Records of North Carolina vol. II)
      - An Act for Facilitating the Navigation of Port Bath, Port Roanoke, and Port Beaufort, 1766, Colonial Records of North Carolina, vol. XXIII, 1990s; 28134; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder An Act for Facilitating the Navigation of Port Bath, Port Roanoke, and Port Beaufort, 1766, Colonial Records of North Carolina, vol. XXIII)
      - Danger at the Inlet, 1775, from Betsy Dowdy's Ride by Nell Wise Wechter, 1990s; 28135; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Danger at the Inlet, 1775, from Betsy Dowdy's Ride by Nell Wise Wechter)
      - The Opening of an Inlet at the Lower End of Albemarle Sound by Archibald D. Murphy, 1819, 1990s; 28136; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder The Opening of an Inlet at the Lower End of Albemarle Sound by Archibald D. Murphy, 1819)
      - Utopian Way of Choosing a Wife by Calvin H. Wiley, 1849, 1990s; 28137; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Utopian Way of Choosing a Wife by Calvin H. Wiley, 1849)
      - Sympathy with North Carolina by T.W. Conway, William Cullen Bryant, 1861, 1990s; 28138; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Sympathy with North Carolina by T.W. Conway, William Cullen Bryant, 1861)
      - The Wreck of the Huron, Contributed by Edna Harris, 1877, 1990s; 28139; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder The Wreck of the Huron, Contributed by Edna Harris, 1877)
      - The Surroundings and Site of Raleigh, Talcott Williams, 1887, 1990s; 28140; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder The Surroundings and Site of Raleigh, Talcott Williams, 1887)
      - Black Fishing at Salter Path by Tristram Tupper, 1990s, 28141; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Black Fishing at Salter Path by Tristram Tupper, 1990s)
      - Isaac Don Levine, 1923, 1990s; 28142; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Isaac Don Levine, 1923)
      - A Last Frontier Joins Civilization by Carolyn L. Reynolds, 1929, 1990s; 28143; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder A Last Frontier Joins Civilization by Carolyn L. Reynolds, 1929)
      - Croatan and Hatteras by William Seeman, 1931, 1990s; 28144; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Croatan and Hatteras by William Seeman, 1931)
      - Cedar Island and the 1933 Hurricane by Adelaide Daniels Day, 1933, 1990s; 28145; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Cedar Island and the 1933 Hurricane by Adelaide Daniels Day, 1933)
      - Excerpt from Duck Boats, Blinds, Decoys, and Eastern Seaboard Wildfowling by Raymond Camp, 1941, 1990s; 28146; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Excerpt from Duck Boats, Blinds, Decoys, and Eastern Seaboard Wildfowling by Raymond Camp, 1941)
      - Lantern on the Beach by Noel Houston, 1943, 1990s; 28147; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Lantern on the Beach by Noel Houston, 1943)
      - So This is Ocracoke by J.J. Dugan, 1950, 1990s; 28148; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder So This is Ocracoke by J.J. Dugan, 1950)
      - Memories of Cedar Island by Jean Day, 1953, 1990s; 28149; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Memories of Cedar Island by Jean Day, 1953)
      - A Built-In Beach Boom by Bill Sharpe, 1961, 1990s; 28150; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder A Built-In Beach Boom by Bill Sharpe, 1961)
      - Annual Pirates Jamboree to Launch Vacation Season on Outer Banks, 1964, 1990s; 28151; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Annual Pirates Jamboree to Launch Vacation Season on Outer Banks, 1964)
      - Where Nature Has the Last Laugh on Man, Hugh Mulligan, 1965, 1990s; 28152; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Where Nature Has the Last Laugh on Man, Hugh Mulligan, 1965)
      - Uncle Jack's Mailbag / Mad About Food, by Jack Sandburg, 1982, 1990s; 28153; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Uncle Jack's Mailbag / Mad About Food, by Jack Sandburg, 1982)
      - Ocracoke Ponies by Ellen Turlington Johnson-Hale, 1986, 1990s; 28154; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Ocracoke Ponies by Ellen Turlington Johnson-Hale, 1986)
      - Outer Banks Dialect by David L. Shores, 1989, 1990s; 28155; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Outer Banks Dialect by David L. Shores, 1989)
      - A One-Act Play Written for the Theatre of the Absurd by Jack Sandburg, 1992, 1990s; 28156; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder A One-Act Play Written for the Theatre of the Absurd by Jack Sandburg, 1992)
      - Outer Banks, 1990s; 28157; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Outer Banks)
      - Corolla and Duck, 1990s; 28158; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Corolla and Duck)
      - Harkers Island, 1990s; 28159; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Harkers Island)
      - Hatteras, 1990s; 28160; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hatteras)
      - Nags Head, 1990s; 28161; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Nags Head)
      - Old Nags Head, 1990s; 28162; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Old Nags Head)
      - Ocracoke Island, 1990s; 28163; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Ocracoke Island)
      - Portsmouth Island, 1990s; 28164; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Portsmouth Island)
      - Roanoke Island, 1990s; 28165; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Roanoke Island)
      - Rodanthe, 1990s; 28166; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Rodanthe)
      - Salter Path, 1990s; 28167; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Salter Path)
      - Other Areas of North Carolina, 1990s; 28168; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Other Areas of North Carolina)
      - Laws of North Carolina, 1990s; 28169; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Laws of North Carolina)
      - Banker Ponies, 1990s; 28170; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Banker Ponies)
      - Beach Erosion, 1990s; 28171; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Beach Erosion)
      - Boating and Shipping, 1990s; 28172; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Boating and Shipping)
      - Commercial and Sport Fishing, 1990s; 28173; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Commercial and Sport Fishing)
      - Theodosia Burr, 1990s; 28174; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Theodosia Burr)
      - Hunting, 1990s; 28175; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hunting)
      - Folklore, Legends, and Myths, 1990s; 28176; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Folklore, Legends, and Myths)
      - Plays, 1990s; 28177; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Plays)
      - The Lost Colony Drama, 1990s; 28178; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder The Lost Colony Drama)
      - Poetry, 1990s; 28179; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Poetry)
      - Hurricanes, 1990s; 28180; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hurricanes)
      - Recipes, 1990s; 28181; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Recipes)
      - Roanoke Island Historical Association, 1990s; 28182; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Roanoke Island Historical Association)
      - Roanoke Voyages and the Lost Colony, 1990s; 28183; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Roanoke Voyages and the Lost Colony)
      - Shipwrecks and the U.S. Lifesaving Service, 1990s; 28184; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Shipwrecks and the U.S. Lifesaving Service)
  - Roanoke Island: The Beginnings of English America, 1947-1984 and undated; 6722; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    - Correspondence, 1981-1983; 28185; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence)
    - Correspondence, Post-Publication, 1983-1984; 28186; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence, Post-Publication)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983; 28187; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
    - Publicity, 1983; 28188; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Publicity)
    - Research Notes: Index, circa 1983; 28189; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Research Notes: Index)
    - Research Notes: Bibliography, circa 1983; 28190; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Research Notes: Bibliography)
    - Research Notes: Lost Colony, 1947-circa 1965; 28191; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Research Notes: Lost Colony)
    - Research Notes: Lost Colony Panel Discussion, 17 July 1959; 28192; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Research Notes: Lost Colony Panel Discussion)
    - Research Notes: Pre-Raleigh Colonies, circa 1983; 28193; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Research Notes: Pre-Raleigh Colonies)
    - Research Notes: Raleigh and Raleigh Colonies, circa 1983; 28194; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Research Notes: Raleigh and Raleigh Colonies)
    - Research Notes: Various, circa 1983; 28195; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Research Notes: Various)
    - Reviews, 1983-1984; 28196; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Reviews)
    - Draft 1, Part 1, 1981; 28197; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 1, Part 1)
    - Draft 1, Part 2, 1981; 28198; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 1, Part 2)
    - Draft 2, Part 2, 1981; 28199; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 2, Part 2)
    - Draft 2, Part 2, 1981; 28200; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 2, Part 2)
    - Draft 3, Part 1, 1982; 28201; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 3, Part 1)
    - Draft 3, Part 2, 1982; 28202; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 3, Part 2)
    - Draft 4, Part 1 (Dough Corrections), 1982; 28203; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 4, Part 1 (Dough Corrections))
    - Draft 4, Part 2 (Dough Corrections), 1982; 28204; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 4, Part 2 (Dough Corrections))
    - Draft 4, Part 1 (Perry Green, Stick, and Dough), 1982; 28205; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 4, Part 1 (Perry Green, Stick, and Dough))
    - Draft 4, Part 2 (Perry Green, Stick, and Dough), 1982; 28206; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 4, Part 2 (Perry Green, Stick, and Dough))
    - Draft 4.1, Chapters 1-4, Dough Corrections (abandoned October 1982), 28207; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 4.1, Chapters 1-4, Dough Corrections (abandoned October 1982))
    - Draft 5, Part 1, 1983; 28208; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 5, Part 1)
    - Draft 5, Part 2, 1983; 28209; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 5, Part 2)
    - Draft 6, Part 1, 1983; 28210; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 6, Part 1)
    - Draft 6, Part 2, 1983; 28211; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 6, Part 2)
    - Page Proofs, 1983; 28212; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Page Proofs)
    - Dust Jacket, 1983; 28213; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dust Jacket)
    - Illustrations, circa 1983; 28214; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Illustrations)
    - Index, 1983; 28215; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Index)
    - Possible Early Draft of Roanoke Island: The Beginnings of English America, undated; 28216; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Possible Early Draft of Roanoke Island: The Beginnings of English America)
  - Speeches and Speaking Engagements, 1952-2006; 6723; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    - Albemarle Sound - College of the Albemarle Conference, 1982; 28217; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Albemarle Sound - College of the Albemarle Conference)
    - Albemarle Schoolmasters, 10 April 1961; 28218; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Albemarle Schoolmasters)
    - American Shore and Beach Preservation Association, 7 May 1962; 28219; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder American Shore and Beach Preservation Association)
    - Aycock Brown Center Dedication [audiocassette], November 1984; 190680; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Aycock Brown Center Dedication [audiocassette])
    - "Bald Head," Wilmington Library Friends [audiocassette], 25 April 1985; 190681; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item "Bald Head," Wilmington Library Friends [audiocassette])
    - Beta Convention, 2 March 1972; 28220; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Beta Convention)
    - Blount, James D. Jr., 21 November 1967; 28221; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Blount, James D. Jr.)
    - Bridge Dedication [Wright Memorial Bridge], 5 November 1966; 28222; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Bridge Dedication [Wright Memorial Bridge])
    - CAMA Speech, Edenton, ARP&DC [audiocassette], 8 August 1974; 190682; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item CAMA Speech, Edenton, ARP&DC [audiocassette])
    - Cape Hatteras Commencement, 30 May 1961; 28223; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Cape Hatteras Commencement)
    - Chamber of Commerce Contract Signing Ceremony, June 1986; 28224; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Chamber of Commerce Contract Signing Ceremony)
    - Chicamacomico Celebration (inserted in Congressional Record), 16 June 1956; 28225; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Chicamacomico Celebration (inserted in Congressional Record))
    - Civil War Conference, Hatteras, October 1999; 28226; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Civil War Conference, Hatteras)
    - Coastal Plains, 5 December 1974; 28227; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Coastal Plains)
    - College of the Albemarle Dare Symposium, 26 April 2006; 28228; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder College of the Albemarle Dare Symposium)
    - College of the Albemarle Seminar, 10 October 1973; 28229; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder College of the Albemarle Seminar)
    - College of the Albemarle Talk, 20 October 2004; 28230; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder College of the Albemarle Talk)
    - The Colony of Carolina - Burgaw, 1 April 1963; 28231; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder The Colony of Carolina - Burgaw)
    - Currituck Library, 13 April 1975; 28232; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Currituck Library)
    - Dare County Arts Council, 16 May 2004; 28233; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dare County Arts Council)
    - Dare County Library, 27 April 1969; 28234; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dare County Library)
    - Duck Woods Golf Club Dedication [audiocassette], 7 June 1969; 190683; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Duck Woods Golf Club Dedication [audiocassette])
    - ECU Seminar, 30 April 1976; 28235; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder ECU Seminar)
    - ECU Speech, 25 April 2002; 28236; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder ECU Speech)
    - Elizabethan Gardens Speeches, 1999-2000; 28237; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Elizabethan Gardens Speeches)
    - EMS Speech, 18-19 May 2003; 28238; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder EMS Speech)
    - English Speaking Union Speech, 6 June 2003; 28239; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder English Speaking Union Speech)
    - Friends of the Library, UNC, 9 April 1985; 28240; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Friends of the Library, UNC)
    - Gates County High School, 29 May 1972; 28241; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Gates County High School)
    - Governors Conference on Economic Development, 1-3 November 1961; 28242; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Governors Conference on Economic Development)
    - Harkers Island (Coastal Federation), 1 June 2006; 28243; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Harkers Island (Coastal Federation))
    - Hurricane Gladys, 28 September 1975; 28244; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hurricane Gladys)
    - Johnston County Library Dedication Program [audiocassette], [1967?]; 190684; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Johnston County Library Dedication Program [audiocassette])
    - Lost Colony Panel etc., 17 July 1959; 28245; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Lost Colony Panel etc.)
    - Manteo High School Commencement, 16 June 1985; 28246; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Manteo High School Commencement)
    - Maritime Heritage Conference, 1980; 28247; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Maritime Heritage Conference)
    - Maritime Heritage Conference, 1981; 28248; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Maritime Heritage Conference)
    - Maritime History Council, 23 October 1998; 28249; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Maritime History Council)
    - Maritime History Slide/Tape Program, 1983; 28250; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Maritime History Slide/Tape Program)
    - Mattamuskeet Speech, 10 April 1999; 28251; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Mattamuskeet Speech)
    - McRae-Elkin Public Library: David Stick and the Governor [1/4" open reel audiotape], circa 1967; 190735; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item McRae-Elkin Public Library: David Stick and the Governor [1/4" open reel audiotape])
    - Metropolis, 3 October 2004; 28252; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Metropolis)
    - Miscellaneous David Stick Speeches, 1973-1979; 28253; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous David Stick Speeches)
    - Miscellaneous Speeches, 1961; 28254; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous Speeches)
    - Miscellaneous Speeches etc., 1970s; 28255; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous Speeches etc.)
    - Miscellaneous Speeches, Writings, etc., 1985; 28256; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous Speeches, Writings, etc.)
    - Museum of the Albemarle, 12 March 1969; 28257; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Museum of the Albemarle)
    - Museum of the Albemarle [audiocassette], 21 January 1980; 190685; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Museum of the Albemarle [audiocassette])
    - National Library Week, 1969; 28258; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder National Library Week)
    - National Library Week: David Stick and Governor Bob Scott [audiocassette], 1969; 190686; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item National Library Week: David Stick and Governor Bob Scott [audiocassette])
    - Ninety-Nines, 24 May 1969; 28259; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Ninety-Nines)
    - North Carolina Association of Professional Engineers [audiocassette], 17 June 1976; 190687; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item North Carolina Association of Professional Engineers [audiocassette])
    - North Carolina Association of Realtors, 1959; 28260; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder North Carolina Association of Realtors)
    - North Carolina Motel Association, 21 May 1976; 28261; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder North Carolina Motel Association)
    - North Carolina People Broadcast, 1982; 28262; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder North Carolina People Broadcast)
    - North Carolina Writer's Conference, 1999-2002; 28263; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder North Carolina Writer's Conference)
    - Onslow Lecture, 1982; 28264; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Onslow Lecture)